Danilo A. da Luz Jr.

professor_luz@hotmail.com | +351 925566296 | Portugal https://www.linkedin.com/in/professorluz/http://www.daniloluz.tech

SUMMARY

Student of the Technologist in Systems Analysis course at Anhanguera College Brazil, he specializes in Photoshop and graphic development with experience in posters, flyers and invitations. He developed the preoperative checklist in Excel for Hospital in São Paulo that is still in use. He worked at IB2B as a Help Desk in the beginning of his career. A creative thinker who enjoys new challenges and teamwork. He has 2 international language certificates (English).

SKILLS

- Organized
- Criative
- Teamwork

- Calm under pressure
- Flexible and adaptable
- Passionate about learning

EXPERIENCE

Health Care Assistant

Marlay Nursing Home | Dublin - Ireland | From: Jul 2022-Fev 2023

- Assist users and check their conditions daily.
- Offer comfort and help to users.
- Report on completed tasks and communicate any changes.
- Be a companion, be prepared to talk and listen to the users' stories.

Professor

Anhanguera College | Sorocaba - SP, Brazil | From: Apr 2018-Jan 2020

- Followed official American Heart Association Manuals to provide relevant and knowledgeable training to class participants. Developed detailed planned and completed lectures to outline CPR course material for students.
- Created appropriate learning environments for students.
- Wrote exams, class material, and writing assignments.

Help Desk Support

Inter Telecon Corp - IB2B | São Paulo - SP, Brazil | From: Aug 2000-Jul 2001

- Provides technical support to users by researching and answering questions, troubleshooting, and maintaining workstation and LAN performance.
- Provided responses to customers by identifying issues, researching answers, and guiding customers through corrective steps.
- Helped users to understand the company's platforms by answering by phone or online chat.

EDUCATION

Technologist: Systems Analysis - Anhanguera |

| Remote - SP/Brazil | From: Jan 2023 to Dez 2024 |

Student at Alura Portal

| Remote - SP/Brazil | From: Fev 2023 |

• Also has training in the health field with Master's, Postgraduate, Bachelor's and Tech degrees.

Portuguese: First Language English: C2 Spanish: A2 Advanced Elementary CERTIFICATIONS

- More than 20 Certificates in Sports, Health and Personal Care, including International Certifications in English and First Aid (Australia).
- Great skills with Office (Advanced) and PDF editor; Expert in Photoshop (Intermediate).

